<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Playground</string>

    <string name="apka1">Przetłumaczyć opis na polski w Tłumaczu Google? Przetłumacz
Become the lord and master of a real medieval castle! Accept new subjects, assign them to their duties, train and protect your men and women! Defy your rivals and laws of physics as you build and upgrade your fortress!

Your pudgy warriors look great in their shining armor! Nourish and train your troops, and they’ll crush the armies of Grav the Mighty Brainpan, find the shelter of the fearsome OM-NOM, put the Abyss Lord back in his place, and also burn down a couple of enemies’ castles!

All day long your scribes scratch their heads with quills, treasurers spill coins on the floor and blacksmiths drop anvils on their feet for the sake of your prosperity! Prepare true specialists, become wealthy and influential! Build a dating room and watch your subjects have children who’ll soon grow up and serve you too!


Assume command, my lord! Here are some of the opportunities you get in the game:

- Story-driven campaign. In hundreds of missions your heroes fight orcs, giants, skeletons and even dragons! Battle magic, cold steel and cunning strategy – the end justifies the means!
- Castle construction. Build new rooms for your stronghold and upgrade the existing ones. You’ve got all you need to create a dream castle! Begin the construction now!
- Developing the villagers. Each of your subjects can learn new skills and wear any equipment. Train great warriors and scribes… and then swap them with each other!
- Multiplayer. Get medieval! Burn and plunder the castle of someone you don’t like… And you don’t like all of them, right?

We are now working on:
- Clans: Join an exciting cooperative gameplay! Create clans together with other players, talk in chat, develop you kingdoms, train your champions, conquer territories and dominate other kingdoms.
- Portals and mazes: even more options to earn unique chests with precious rewards. New enemies, new bosses and new territories!
- Caravans: if you are tired of war, go into business!
- The extension of the storyline campaign: get to the chief villain and triumph over the universal evil!
- Collections and unique heroes
- Daily log-in bonuses
- The improvement of the visual elements of the game
- The optimization and balance of the game process
- Performance improvements
All of these and many other innovations are waiting for you in the upcoming updates!</string>


    <string name="apka2">Duel players from all around the world in the best real-time game! Collect and upgrade 40+ troops and spells: from the lovely Dryad to the tremendous Dragon! Play now, for free!

Lead your army to victory! Build a strong deck and crush your enemy\'s castle deploying your troops! Earn trophies and climb the global ranking! Open your chests to discover and unlock new powerful warriors and spells! Will you get one of the magic legendary cards?

Define your strategy and choose your warriors carefully. Archers to kill from a distance? A Golem to break through the defense? Or a heal spell to give a boost to your troops? Your decision will make the difference between victory and defeat!

FEATURES
 Duel other players in epic battles
 Collect new powerful troops
 Destroy opponent\’s castles to unlock new cards
 Progress through multiple levels all the way to the top
 Learn different battle tactics and become the ultimate champion
 Free Daily cards
 Open magical chests
 Earn trophies
 Join a legendary clan
 Fun, intuitive mechanics
 Real-time duelling game
 Play for free!
 Ideal for all types of players - kids and adults, girls and boys...

Get into the arena and clash against other players on epic battles! The combat may be hard, prepare your strategy to win this pvp war game!

One of the best multiplayer strategy games! Join now this epic card game and have fun fighting your enemies.

Join the Castle Crush community:
Facebook Page
Forums</string>
</resources>
